

CONTACT ME AT

- J-403 ADORE HAPPY HOMES SECTOR 86 FARIDABAD 121002
- wadhwapratham7@gmail.com
- 8006669857

SKILLS SUMMARY

- $\bullet \bullet \bullet \bullet \bullet \quad \mathsf{HTML/Bootstrap/CSS/jquery}$
- •••• Shopify Web Development.
- •••• Photoshop
- •••• Wix website builder.

PRATHAM WADHWA

SHOPIFY WEB DEVELOPER

PERSONAL PROFILE

Creative, enthusiastic, and task-driven professional with 3+ years of experience in the field of web design and development across various projects. Experienced in developing custom themes and managing ecommerce stores. I am looking forward to a company that supports learning and growth of its employees as well as provides work life balance.

EDUCATIONAL HISTORY

ECHELON INSTITUTE OF TECHNOLOGY

Bachelors in computer application | 2018 - 2021

RISHABH ACADEMY

10+2 | Meerut

- CGPA in 10th 8.8.
- Completed high school in 2018 with 77%.

WORK EXPERIENCE

Frontend Developer (shopify)

MOBIKASA | Apr 2023. - Present

- Solely managing website development and maintenance.
- Developing landing pages for different campaigns.
- Worked on website speed optimisations.

Shopify Web developer

LYXEL&FLAMINGO | Apr 2022 - Present

- Working on multiple shopify projects.
- Developed custom theme.
- Managed backend for stores.

Front End Developer

Creative Orion | dec 2021 - mar 2022

- Worked on wordpress websites.
- Created wordpress website using elementor and worked on custom theme as well.
- Created website on shopify.

WEB DESIGNER/ QUALITY ASSURANCE

Adaan digital solutions | aug 2021 - nov 2021

- Replicated websites from mono to wix. Collaborated with other designers
- Worked as an Quality Assurance doing testing and post testing for websites designs.

Front End Developer/ Graphic Designer

Code Crew | sep 2020 - jul2021

- Worked on wordpress websites.
- Designed UI for various projects.
- Worked on shopify custom themes.
- Designed webdesigns infographs etc on photoshop.

PROJECTS

- Kawaii Amai https://www.kawaiiamai.com
- Mayandco https://mayandco.in
- Newu https://www.newu.in
- Jaquline USA https://jaqulineusa.com
- Amala Earth https://amala.earth
- Govo life https://www.govo.life
- Biotique https://www.biotique.com
- Active Beaute https://activbeaute.com
- Yahvi https://www.yahvi.co.in
- Chicasuu https://chicasuu.com
- MilleSuperGrain https://millesupergrain.com
- Instax FujiFilms https://www.instax.in
- KLF Nirmal: https://www.klfnirmal.com/
- Members Only: https://membersonly.com/
- Neutraleaf India: https://neutraleafindia.com/
- Araya: https://ary-fj.myshopify.com/
- Devatri Wellness
- HaldiramsUk: https://haldiramsonline.myshopify.com/
- Main Hardware: https://main-hardwares.myshopify.com/
- Grab To Cart: https://grabtocart-store.myshopify.com/
- yufoodlabs: https://yufoodlabs.com/
- Randolph USA: https://randolphusa.com
- Petland Canada: https:// petland.ca
- Reranger: https://www.reranger.com/